<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<doc>
    <para type="preview">While visiting her family home in Edenton, North Carolina, Jacobs writes to
        Ednah Dow Cheney of the New England Freedman's Aid Society. "Thank God, the bitter cup is
        drained of its last dreg. There is no more need of hiding places to conceal slave
        Mothers."</para>

    <letter>
        <line type="header">
            <location town="Edenton" state="North Carolina">Edenton [North Carolina]</location>
            <date month="April" day="25th" year="1867">April 25*th* [1867]</date>
        </line>

        <line type="greeting">Dear <person>Mrs Cheeny</person></line>

        <para type="body">I felt I would like to write you a line from my old <place>home</place>. I am sitting
            under the old roof. <num>twelve</num> <unit>feet</unit> from the spot where I suffered all the crushing weight
            of slavery. thank <diety>God</diety>, the bitter cup is drained of its last dreg. There is no more need
            of hiding places to conceal slave Mothers. yet it was little to purchase the blessings
            of freedom. I could have worn this poor life out there to save my Children from the
            misery and degradation of Slavery.</para>

        <para type="body">I had long thought I had no attachment to my old <place>home</place>. As I often sit here
            and think of those I loved of their hard struggle in life—their unfaltering love and
            devotion toward myself and Children. I love to sit here and think of them. they have
            made the few sunny spots in that dark life sacred to me.</para>

        <para type="body">I cannot tell you how I feel in this <place>place</place>. the change is so great I can
            hardly take it all in I was born here. and amid all these new born blessings. the old
            dark cloud comes over me. and I find it hard to have faith in rebels.</para>

        <para type="body">the past <season>winter</season> was very severe for this region of <place>Country</place> it caused much
            suffering—and the freedmen with but few exceptions were cheated out of their crop of
            cotton. their <profession>contract masters</profession> shiped it for them. and when they ask for a settlement.
            they are answered I am daily expecting the returns. these men have gone to work
            cheerfully. planted another crop without the returns to live on until their present crop
            is made. Many of the large <place>plantations</place> of the once wealthy <profession>Planter</profession>. is worked under the
            control of colored men. the Owners let their <place>Plantations</place> to the freed men in prefference
            to the poor whites— they believe the Negro determined to make money. and they will get
            the largest portion of it. last years experience I think will be a proffitable lesson
            many will learn to act for themselves Negro suffrage is making a stir in this place. the
            rebels are striving to make these <emphasis>*people*</emphasis> feel they are their true
            friends. and they must not be led astray by the Yankees. the
                <missing>[freedmen]</missing> ask if <person type="president">Abraham Lincoln</person> led t<missing>[hem]</missing>
            astray. that his friends is their <missing>[friends]</missing> his enemies their
            enemies.</para>

        <para type="body">I have spent much of my <missing>[time on?]</missing> the <place>Plantations</place>
            distributing seed and trying to teach the women to make Yankee gardens. they plant
            everything to mature in the <season>summer</season>. like their corn and cotton fields. I have hunted up
            all the old people. done what I could for them. I love to work for these old people.
            many of them I have known from Childhood there is one <place>School</place> in <town>Edenton</town> well attended.
            on some of the <place>Plantations</place> there is from <num>15</num> to <num>25 </num>Children that cannot attend <place>School.</place>
            the distance is so far. some of the freedmen are very anxious to establish <place>Plantation</place>
            <place>schools.</place> as soon as the more advanced <place>Schools</place>. can send out <profession>teachers</profession>. many of the
            freedmen are willing and will sustain their <profession>teachers</profession>. at <emphasis>*present*</emphasis>
            there is a great revival in the Colored <place type="religious">Churches</place> the whites say the niggers sung and
            prayed until they got their freedom. and they are not satisfied. now they are singing
            and praying for judjment. the white members of the Baptist <place type="religious">Church</place> invited the colored
            members to their Church. to help them sing and pray. I assure you they have done it with
            a will. I never saw such a state of excitment. the <place type="religious">Churches</place> have been open night and
            day. these people have time to think of their souls. now they are not compeled to think
            for the Negro.</para>

        <line type="closing">My love to <person>Miss Daisy.</person> I send her some Jassamine blossoms tell her they
            bear the fragrance of freedom. Yours Truly</line>

        <line type="signature">H Jacobs</line>
    </letter>

    <line type="title">Citation:</line>
    <line type="sources">Autograph letter, signed; <person>Sophia Smith</person> Collection.</line>
</doc>
