<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="chan_RNGEx2_Sept8.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
    <metadata><title>A PILGRIMAGE TO THE REAL LIFE LOCATIONS OF YOUR NAME </title><subtitle>A
            STEP-BY-STEP ANIME WALKING TOUR YOU CAN FOLLOW</subtitle>
        <date when="2017-10-03"/>OCTOBER 3, 2017 • <credit type="author"><wordCount num="3780"/>3780
            WORDS WRITTEN BY <person xml:id="nakamine">KANAE NAKAMINE</person></credit> • <credit
            type="art">ART BY <person ref="nakamine">KANAE NAKAMINE</person> AND <person
                xml:id="hayakawa">SHUN HAYAKAWA</person></credit>
    </metadata>
    <p>During my vacation to <loc xml:id="jp">Japan </loc>this summer, I went on a pilgrimage. But
        this wasn't a religious pilgrimage—this was an <term ref="anime">anime</term>
        pilgrimage.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>Actually, certain people might consxml:ider <term xml:id="anime">anime</term> a religious
        experience. Maybe that's why Japanese people have started using the term
                <term><romanji>seichijunrei</romanji>
            <tradJP><kanji>聖地巡礼</kanji>せいちじゅんれい</tradJP></term> to describe visiting real-life
        locations used in <term ref="anime">anime</term>
        <comment>this word is usually reserved for trips to sacred places</comment>.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>It makes sense when you think of the connection some people have with <term ref="anime"
            >anime</term>. Personally, I felt a special connection with the film <filmName>Your
            Name</filmName>, which took the Japanese box office by storm in 2016 <comment>Tofugu
            loved it so much, we added it to our list of Top 20 <term ref="anime">anime</term> of
            all time</comment>. I loved the story and characters of course, but the illustrated
        backgrounds are what moved me most.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>Director <person xml:id="makoto">Shinkai Makoto</person> captured the breathtaking,
        beautiful scenery of <loc ref="tokyo">Tokyo</loc> in intricate detail. As a former Tokyoite,
        this made an impact on me. The hand-drawn cityscapes really pulled me into the story.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>So when I visited <loc ref="tokyo">Tokyo</loc> during my vacation this past summer, I decxml:ided
        to go on an <term ref="anime">anime</term> pilgrimage and visit locations used in
            <filmName>Your Name</filmName>. It was such an awesome experience that I wanted to share
        my personal walking tour with you; 15 sacred <filmName>Your Name</filmName> locations in one
        day.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>If you love the film, I hope this is something you can do on your next trip to <loc
            ref="tokyo">Tokyo</loc>.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>
        <note>Note: If you haven't seen the movie yet… sorry, this article is full of spoilers
                <comment>naturally</comment>. Proceed at your own spoil-y risk.</note>
    </p>
    <br/>
    <ul type="TOC">
        <li id = "1">Before You Start a Your Name Pilgrimage…</li>
        <li id = "2">Your Name Pilgrimage Itinerary</li>
        <li id = "3">Salon de Thé Rond <time><timeRange start="1055" end="1145">10:55–11:45
                    a.m.</timeRange></time>
            <note>Closed on Tues</note></li>
        <li id = "4">The National Art Center <time><timeRange start="1145" end="1245">11:45–12:45
                    a.m.</timeRange></time>
            <note>Closed on Tues</note></li>
        <li id = "5">Tokyo City View in Roppongi Hills <time><timeRange start="1300" end="1400"
                    >1:00–2:00 p.m.</timeRange></time></li>
        <li id = "6">Yotsuya Station <time><timeRange start="1425" end="1440">2:25–2:40
                    p.m.</timeRange></time></li>
        <li id = "7">On the Way to <loc ref="suga">Suga Shrine</loc>
            <time><timeRange start="1440" end="1520">2:40–3:20 p.m.</timeRange></time></li>
        <li id = "8">Suga Shrine Stairs <time><timeRange start="1520" end="1600">3:20–4:00
                    p.m.</timeRange></time></li>
        <li id = "9">
            <loc ref="mmpg">Meiji Memorial Picture Gallery</loc>
            <time>
                <timeRange start="1620" end="1630">4:20–4:30 p.m</timeRange>
            </time>
        </li>
        <li id = "10">Around <loc ref="shinanomachiSt">Shinanomachi Station</loc>
            <time><timeRange start="1800" end="1830">6:00–6:30 p.m.</timeRange></time></li>
        <li id = "11">
            <loc ref="yunika">Yunika Vision</loc>
            <time>
                <timeRange start="1850" end="1910">6:50–7:10 p.m.</timeRange>
            </time>
        </li>
        <li id = "12">Shintoshin Pedestrian Brxml:idge near Takarazuka University <time><timeRange
                    start="1920" end="1940">7:20–7:40 p.m.</timeRange></time></li>
        <li id = "13">Intersection Behind Shinjuku Police Station <time><timeRange start="1945"
                    end="2000">7:45–8:00 p.m.</timeRange></time></li>
        <li id = "14">Cafe La Bohéme near Shinjuku Gyoen <time><timeRange start="2030" end="2200"
                    >8:30–10:00 p.m.</timeRange></time></li>
        <li id = "15">Following the Red Thread to Your Name Locations</li>
    </ul>
    <heading ref="1">BEFORE YOU START A YOUR NAME PILGRIMAGE…</heading>
    <p>Here are some things to prepare/keep in mind before you set off on your religious <term
            ref="anime">anime</term> journey:</p>
    <br/>
    <p>Many places in this article are close to each other so most of the time, walking will be your
        best option <comment>a pilgrimage should be full of walking anyway</comment>. I recommend
        wearing comfortable shoes and staying hydrated if you're going in summer. Summer in <loc
            ref="jp">Japan </loc>is insanely hot.</p>
    <p>I timed my visits so the lighting conditions at each location would roughly match what is
        seen in the film. But most of the itinerary ordering is just for convenient transportation.
        Also, the itinerary is based on my July visit, so if you're traveling in a different season
        you may have to adjust your plans.</p>
    <p>I know you want to take great photos on this trip <comment>I dxml:id too</comment>, but be
        mindful of traffic and other people when trying to get that perfect shot. Don't stand in the
        mxml:iddle of the road or on a table at a restaurant just to improve your photography.</p>
    <p>You might run into other <term ref="anime">anime</term> pilgrims <comment>I dxml:id, a few
            times</comment>. Try not to occupy a spot for too long and let other people get in to
        take their pictures too.</p>
    <p>You'll probably be super excited when you recognize these place from Your Name, but try not
        to scream or dance. A lot of the stops are in ordinary neighborhoods where people live and
        work, so be respectful of their living space.</p>
    <heading ref="2">YOUR NAME PILGRIMAGE ITINERARY</heading>
    <p>If you want to find the exact location of each place, check out the handy multi-pin map I
        made on Google Maps.</p>
    <br/>
    <heading ref="3">SALON DE THÉ ROND <comment>10:55–11:45 A.M.</comment> *CLOSED ON
        TUES.</heading>
    <p>THE WATER GLASSES AND COASTERS THE CAFE USES ARE SIMILAR TO THE ONES IN THE MOVIE. THE PLATES
        LOOK IDENTICAL TOO!</p>
    <br/>
    <p>I started my pilgrimage in <loc xml:id="roppongi">Roppongi</loc> where <char xml:id="taki"
            >Taki</char> went on a date with his crush at the time, <char xml:id="okudera"
            >Okudera-senpai</char>.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>In the movie, they start their date in <loc ref="roppongi">Roppongi Hills</loc>, but the
        first stop on our pilgrimage is the coffee shop where they had lunch. It's called <loc
            xml:id="salon">Salon de Thé Rond</loc>, located on the second floor of the<loc
            xml:id="artcentre"> National Art Center</loc>.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>There's no admission fee to get into the building, so you have free access to this coffee
        shop. It opens at <time tm="1100">11:00 a.m.</time> so I went up to the third floor a little
        before then and took some pictures from above. From this angle, I got a great shot of the
        modern, stylish architecture of the museum and the coffee shop.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>fancy coffee shop featured in your name</picalt>
    <p>As soon as <time tm="1100">11:00 a.m.</time> rolled around, I went into the coffee shop for
        an early lunch. I was the first customer! They dxml:idn't serve exactly the same dish <char
            ref="taki">Taki</char> and <char ref="okudera">Okudera-senpai</char> ate in the film, so
        I picked the closest thing I could find which was a sandwich and corn soup meal. The portion
        size was small, but it filled me up enough to walk the rest of the day.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>food at salon de the rond</picalt>
    <p>This is a small thing, but the water glasses and coasters the cafe uses are similar to the
        ones in the movie. The plates look xml:identical too! Just a nice detail for all us Your Name
        superfans out there.</p>
    <br/>
    <heading ref="4">THE NATIONAL ART CENTER <comment>11:45–12:45 A.M.</comment> *CLOSED ON
        TUES.</heading>
    <p>After lunch, I explored the <loc ref="artcentre">National Art Center</loc>. I've visited for
        art exhibitions before, but this time I focused on the space around the exhibits. After
        seeing Your Name, I had a much greater appreciation for the architecture.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>If you watch the movie carefully, you'll notice the finer details of the museum aren't
        replicated exactly, but the signature features of the building <comment>the glass maps and
            wooden walls</comment> are there. They really help you picture <char ref="taki"
            >Taki</char> and <char ref="okudera">Okudera-senpai</char> as an urban couple.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>national art center in your name</picalt>
    <p>During my visit, there were a few art exhibits going on. I checked out one showing
        contemporary art from <loc xml:id="SEAsia">Southeast Asia</loc>. This wasn't related to the
        movie, but going to art exhibitions in <loc ref="roppongi">Roppongi</loc> is a classic date
        for <loc ref="tokyo">Tokyo</loc> locals. So taking in the art is like walking in <char
            ref="taki">Taki</char> and <char ref="okudera">Okudera-senpai</char>'s footsteps.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>national art center in roppongi</picalt>
    <p><note>Sxml:ide note: if you're visiting <loc ref="tokyo">Tokyo</loc> in <date month="nov"
            />November or<date month="dec"/> December this year <comment><date year="2017"
                />2017</comment>, the <loc ref="artcentre">National Art Center</loc> will have a
                <person ref="makoto">Shinkai Makoto</person> art exhibit. Checking out original art
            by the director of Your Name in a location from Your Name; that might be the ultimate
                <term ref="anime">anime</term> pilgrimage experience</note>.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>I can't make it, so let me know how it is.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>And if you're reading this after <date year="2017"/>2017, sorry. The otaku event of your
        dreams is over and will never come again.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>The next spot is an observation deck in <loc ref="roppongi">Roppongi Hills</loc>. You can
        walk there from the <loc ref="artcentre">National Art Center</loc> in about <time
            duration="15">fifteen minutes</time>.</p>
    <br/>
    <heading ref="5">TOKYO CITY VIEW IN ROPPONGI HILLS <comment>1:00–2:00 P.M.</comment></heading>
    <p>IN YOUR NAME, TAKI AND OKUDERA-SENPAI GO TO THE OBSERVATION DECK CALLED TOKYO CITY VIEW.</p>
    <br/>
    <p><loc ref="roppongi">Roppongi Hills</loc> is a huge complex of commercial facilities like
        shops, movie theaters, and restaurants. In Your Name, <char ref="taki">Taki</char> and <char
            ref="okudera">Okudera-senpai</char> go to the observation deck called <loc xml:id="tcv"
            >Tokyo City View</loc>. It costs at least <money cost="1800">¥1,800</money> to get in,
        but sometimes you have to sacrifice for your <term ref="anime">anime</term> journey.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>Unfortunately, during my visit to the observation deck, there was a partition blocking part
        of the space, so I couldn't back up far enough to get a photo with a composition similar to
        the one in the movie.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>Besxml:ides that, I had a great time. It was my first time at <loc ref="tcv">Tokyo City
            View</loc> and I got to see the city landscape stretching out all the way to Tokyo
        Tower. It was an awesome view!</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>tokyo city view in your name and roppongi</picalt>
    <p>If you've got time, there's an art gallery <comment>on the same floor) and an art museum (one
            floor down</comment>. My ticket to the observation deck included the downstairs art
        museum too, so I popped in there for a bit.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>The next stop is <time duration="25">twenty-five minutes</time> away. So we'll need to hop on
        the <loc xml:id="oedo">Ōedo line</loc> from <loc ref="roppongi">Roppongi</loc> Station to
        get there.</p>
    <br/>
    <heading ref="6">YOTSUYA STATION <comment>2:25–2:40 P.M.</comment></heading>
    <p>This is the station where <char ref="taki">Taki</char> and <char ref="okudera"
            >Okudera-senpai</char> meet up for their date. I know I reversed the order of the places
        they visited, but I dxml:id this to avoxml:id the crowds and get better photos. Order and timing
        will make or break an <term ref="anime">anime</term> pilgrimage.</p>
    <br/>
    <p><loc xml:id="yotsuyaSt">Yotsuya Station</loc> also shows up later in the film when <char
            ref="taki">Taki</char> and <char ref="okudera">Okudera-senpai</char> meet up to take a
        walk and talk about their trip to <loc xml:id="itomori">Itomori-chō</loc> a few years
        before.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>If you want to get the best shot, leave the station from the <loc xml:id="akasaka">Akasaka
            exit</loc>. Turn around and look back…</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>yotsuyaSt station exit</picalt>
    <p>You'll get a photo similar to the scene above.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>Now turn to your right…</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>real life location in your name film</picalt>
    <p>Snap a photo of this iconic view.</p>
    <br/>

    <p>There's also these stairs on your righthand sxml:ide, if you're facing the station.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>yotsuyaSt station steps in your name anime</picalt>
    <p><loc ref="yotsuyaSt">Yotsuya Station</loc> is a major commuter station, so be careful with
        crowds while you take pictures.</p>
    <br/>

    <p>Next, let's walk to <loc xml:id="suga">Suga Shrine</loc>; it only takes about <time
            duration="15">fifteen minutes</time>
        <comment>though I stopped at a few Your Name places on my way there</comment>.</p>
    <br/>
    <heading ref="7">ON THE WAY TO SUGA SHRINE <comment>2:40–3:20 P.M.</comment></heading>
    <p>The spots between <loc ref="yotsuyaSt">Yotsuya Station</loc> and <loc ref="suga">Suga
            Shrine</loc> are pretty important for us Your Name fans; they're featured during the
        climax of the film when <char ref="taki">Taki</char> and <char xml:id="mitsuha"
            >Mitsuha</char> are trying to find each other <comment>you know, the part where you were
            crying so hard you could barely see the screen</comment>.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>japanese street signs</picalt>
    <p>Here's one of the spots. Do you recognize these signs? If you do, congratulations! You
        deserve the title: Your Name nerd. This scene was like less than a second long in the movie.
            <comment>How many times have you seen it, anyway?</comment></p>
    <br/>

    <p>From <loc ref="yotsuyaStSt">Yotsuya Station</loc>, head toward <loc xml:id="yotsuyaSan"
            >Yotsuya Sanchōme</loc>, walking on the left sxml:ide of the street, <loc xml:id="shinjuku"
            >Shinjuku Dōri</loc>. You'll run into a Lawson 100 convenience store. Take a left from
        there. You'll see these signs!</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>fork in the road at mitsumata</picalt>
    <p>When you're done adoring this spot, go back to <loc ref="shinjuku">Shinjuku Dōri</loc> and
        keep walking the same direction.</p>
    <br/>

    <p>Not far from the last spot, you'll find a Softbank, then a Kinko's. Take a left again and
        keep going down the street.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>japanese post box used in your name <term ref="anime">anime</term> movie</picalt>
    <p>You'll find a crossroads with this postbox.</p>
    <br/>

    <p>At the crossroads, take the wxml:ider path on your left. You'll end up at the next spot.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>intersection leading to suga shrine</picalt>
    <p>It's another intersection close to the shrine's stairs <comment>you Your Name otaku out there
            know how special the stairs are going to be</comment>.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>When I was here, a bike was left in nearly the same spot as in the movie! I almost moved it
        to the exact same position to get the perfect photo… but that would have been bad manners in
            <loc ref="jp">Japan </loc><comment>or anywhere, really</comment>. So don't do it, if
        you're thinking about it.</p>
    <br/>

    <p>Now hold on to your butts. Here comes the highlight of the entire pilgrimage.</p>
    <br/>
    <heading ref="8">SUGA SHRINE STAIRS <comment>3:20–4:00 P.M.</comment></heading>
    <p>The stairs of <loc ref="suga">Suga Shrine</loc> are the absolute culmination of the film. The
        scene is definitely the most impressive and iconic in all of Your Name. You probably
        remember it from the promotional images before you even saw the movie.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>suga shrine staircase in real life</picalt>
    <p>Of course, this promotional image <comment>with <char ref="taki">Taki</char> and <char
                ref="mitsuha">Mitsuha</char> in school uniforms</comment> isn't replicated exactly
        in the film itself. Also the buildings on the right sxml:ide of the stairs are a little
        different in real life. But you know those artists, always emphasizing height differences to
        make things more dramatic.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>The background used in the actual film is much closer to reality.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>suga shrine steps in your name <term ref="anime">anime</term> film</picalt>
    <p>THE STAIRS OF SUGA SHRINE ARE THE ABSOLUTE CULMINATION OF THE FILM. THE SCENE IS DEFINITELY
        THE MOST IMPRESSIVE AND ICONIC IN ALL OF YOUR NAME.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>When I was here, there were a few other pilgrims; some Japanese high school girls and Chinese
        tourists. They took their pictures and quickly and left, probably off to the rest of the
        locations on the pilgrimage.</p>
    <br/>
    <p><loc ref="suga">Suga Shrine</loc> is a super ordinary place. If you haven't seen Your Name,
        it won't seem special at all. A random guy talked to me at the top of stairs, wondering why
        I was taking pictures of the street and not the shrine behind me. He was visiting for shrine
        purposes and dxml:idn't have any xml:idea why people were there but not visiting the shrine.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>Of course, it's a sacred place for Your Name pilgrims like you and me. For some reason, I had
        trouble leaving this place. I just dxml:idn't want to…</p>
    <br/>
    <p>But, I'm a grownup. I finally left and headed to the next spot: <loc xml:id="mmpg">Meiji
            Memorial Picture Gallery</loc> in <loc xml:id="meiji">Meiji Jingu Gaien-mae</loc>. It's
        a bit far from <loc ref="suga">Suga Shrine</loc>, but still within walking distance. You can
        get there in about <time duration="20">twenty minutes</time>.</p>
    <br/>

    <heading ref="9">MEIJI MEMORIAL PICTURE GALLERY <comment>4:20–4:30 P.M.</comment></heading>
    <p>This scene isn't particularly important in the film, but I recognized the <loc ref="mmpg"
            >Meiji Memorial Picture Gallery</loc> building from one of the scenes where <char
            ref="mitsuha">Mitsuha</char> and <char ref="taki">Taki</char> switch bodies, and <char
            ref="mitsuha">Mitsuha</char> is excited to see Tokyo <comment>I personally really like
            those scenes</comment>. So, I decxml:ided to include it in the pilgrimage.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>meiji memorial picture gallery</picalt>
    <p>Actually, this is the moment I got most hyped during the whole pilgrimage. Check out the sign
        behind those three guys, the green one with the beer on it. It was actually there at the
        real life location! I dxml:idn't expect this at all, because it's an advertisement for a beer
        garden, which is a summer-only restaurant. Pretty lucky, eh? It won't be there forever.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>I read online that the coffee shop the characters went to after this scene <comment><char
                ref="mitsuha">Mitsuha</char> always wanted to visit a fancy Tokyo coffee shop,
            remember?</comment> is modeled after one from this area. Unfortunately, it closed down
        for good so we'll never know how accurate it was. 😭</p>
    <br/>
    <p>I wanted to get a shot of the next spot at dusk so I went back to <loc xml:id="shinanochoSt"
            >Shinanochō Station</loc> for a one hour break at a coffee shop <comment>I was getting
            tired anyway</comment>. If you go on this pilgrimage in winter instead of summer, you
        may not need to wait for dusk because of the daylight time difference.</p>
    <br/>

    <heading ref="10">AROUND SHINANOMACHI STATION <comment>6:00–6:30 P.M.</comment></heading>
    <p>After the coffee, I was refreshed and ready to start my pilgrimage again. This time I headed
        to <loc xml:id="shinanomachiSt">Shinanomachi Station</loc> for two pilgrimage spots.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>One is a pedestrian brxml:idge stretching over the road in front of <loc ref="shinanomachiSt"
            >Shinanomachi Station</loc>. It shows up twice in the film, at the end of both times
            <char ref="taki">Taki</char> meets <char ref="okudera">Okudera-senpai</char>.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>Personally, I resonated more with the scene after the date <comment>the first time they
            met</comment>, because this is where <char ref="taki">Taki</char> starts having feelings
        for <char ref="mitsuha">Mitsuha</char>. After <char ref="okudera">Okudera-senpai</char>
        leaves, <char ref="taki">Taki</char> gets a text from <char ref="mitsuha">Mitsuha</char> and
        then tries to call her.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>pedestrian brxml:idge in your name</picalt>
    <p>Although the brxml:idge and trees looked same, there was a building there in real life that
        wasn't in the movie. Excuse me, building, but you're not canon!</p>
    <br/>

    <p>Nearby the pedestrian brxml:idge, there's a famous landmark of the Shinjuku/Yoyogi area: the <loc
            xml:id="NTT">NTT Docomo Yoyogi Building</loc>, which also shows up in Your Name.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>ntt docomo tower in shinjuku</picalt>
    <p>If you exit the brxml:idge on the station sxml:ide, you'll see the tower at a similar angle to what
        you'll see in the film.</p>
    <br/>

    <p>Next I headed to the Shinjuku area. Take the JR Chūō Line for about <time duration="6">six
            minutes</time> to <loc xml:id="shinjukuSt">Shinjuku Station</loc>.</p>
    <br/>
    <heading ref="11">YUNIKA VISION <comment>6:50–7:10 P.M.</comment></heading>
    <p>The first stop in Shinjuku is <loc xml:id="yunika">Yunika Vision</loc>. It's a giant piece
        of digital signage that broadcasts news footage and advertisements. In the film, commuters
        watched the screen for coverage of the fall of the Tiamat comet.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>yunika vision with tiamat comet</picalt>
    <p>To get to <loc ref="yunika">Yunika Vision</loc>, leave through the east exit of <loc
            ref="shinjukuSt">Shinjuku Station</loc>. With the station to your back, take a left,
        then keep walking straight, parallel with the train line. You'll hit <loc ref="yunika"
            >Yunika Vision</loc> in about <time duration="3">three minutes</time>.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>This is the most crowded place on our itinerary so be careful of pedestrians when taking
        pictures.</p>
    <br/>

    <p>Now it's time to move to the other sxml:ide of Shinjuku. Stay on the same sxml:ide of the street,
        across from <loc ref="yunika">Yunika Vision</loc>. Head under the railway brxml:idge.</p>
    <br/>
    <heading ref="12">SHINTOSHIN PEDESTRIAN BRIDGE NEAR TAKARAZUKA UNIVERSITY <comment>7:20–7:40
            P.M.</comment></heading>
    <p>After about <time duration="7">seven minutes</time> of walking, you'll see a pedestrian
        brxml:idge.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>your name real life location</picalt>
    <p>Remember this? This is the scene where <char ref="taki">Taki</char> and <char ref="mitsuha"
            >Mitsuha</char> cross paths in the snow <comment>they kind of recognize each other but
            don't acknowledge it</comment>.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>If you want to view the brxml:idge from a similar angle to the film, stop near Cafe Veloce.</p>
    <br/>

    <p>If you walk up to the pedestrian brxml:idge, you'll see another scene from Your Name…</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>pedestrian brxml:idge in tokyo</picalt>
    <p>REMEMBER THIS? THIS IS THE SCENE WHERE TAKI AND MITSUHA CROSS PATHS IN THE SNOW <comment>THEY
            KIND OF RECOGNIZE EACH OTHER BUT DON'T ACKNOWLEDGE IT</comment>.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>Of course, it wasn't snowing when I was here in July, but check out those familiar letters in
        the window on the left sxml:ide.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>In the film the blue letters are a logo plus "Chonschon<comment>?</comment>," but in reality
        the letters say "Johnson" with the logo in place of the letter "J." Turns out,
        Johnchonschonson is a translation company. Thankfully, they all work late so the lights were
        on in the office when I took this photo.</p>
    <br/>

    <p>The next spot isn't too far away, just a <time duration="5">five minute</time> walk, but the
        route there is confusing and it's easy to get lost if you don't know the way. For those not
        using Google Maps, here are the directions:</p>
    <br/>
    <p>Exit the pedestrian brxml:idge nearest the building with the big curvy slxml:ide thing on the sxml:ide of
        it <comment>you'll know it when you see it</comment>. You'll see a Family Mart and a
        Starbucks on the right sxml:ide of the building. Go straight and take a left after you cross the
        first intersection. Keep going and you'll find LOVE. Sorry, lonely hearts, in this case LOVE
        is a statue by American artist Robert Indiana.</p>
    <br/>
    <heading ref="13">INTERSECTION BEHIND SHINJUKU POLICE STATION <comment>7:45–8:00
        P.M.</comment></heading>
    <p>After passing by LOVE, you'll see our next sacred pilgrimage spot.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>traffic light used in your name anime</picalt>
    <p>In the film, this traffic light is featured during a short time lapse, after <char
            ref="mitsuha">Mitsuha</char> and <char ref="taki">Taki</char> first realize they've
        switched bodies. If you're familiar with Shinjuku you might recognize the building directly
        behind it: cocoon tower.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>If you want to snap a pic with a similar angle, try a wxml:ide angle lens <comment>unfortunately,
            I dxml:idn't have one</comment>. Also, don't stand in the road! I saw a few other Your Name
        pilgrims standing in the street trying to snap their photos and it looked dangerous to say
        the least.</p>
    <br/>

    <p>The next stop on the pilgrimage is a bit far, but I walked anyway <comment>it takes about
                <time duration="25">twenty-five minutes</time></comment>. Walking through Shinjuku
        is fun, so it's worth the extra time, I think.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>You could also take the Tokyo Metro: hop on the Marunouchi line from Nishi-Shinjuku Station
        and get off at Shinjukugyoen-mae Station.</p>
    <br/>
    <heading ref="14">CAFE LA BOHÉME NEAR SHINJUKU GYOEN <comment>8:30–10:00
        P.M.</comment></heading>
    <p>We've finally come to the grand finale of our pilgrimage. The last stop is the restaurant
        where <char ref="taki">Taki</char> and <char ref="okudera">Okudera-senpai</char> work. In
        reality, the restaurant is called Cafe La Bohéme <tradJP>カフェ ラ・ボエム</tradJP>.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>restaurant where taki works in your name</picalt>
    <p>In Your Name, the restaurant is bigger and located next to a busy road, but the actual spot
        is in a nice, quiet area next to Shinjuku Gyoen.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>One of our dear readers let us know that the name of the restaurant in the movie, Il Giardino
        delle Parole, means "The Garden of Words" in Italian. No need to explain for fans of
        Shinkai's work, but that's the name of his previous movie, which was based on Shinjuku
        Gyoen. Such a neat detail!</p>
    <br/>
    <p>The restaurant is not-too-casual and they have a dress code. If you want to come in to eat
        and take photos, don't wear sweatpants, shorts, T-shirts, or Pikachu pajamas.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>I celebrated the end of my pilgrimage with dinner at this restaurant. I was there at 8:00
        p.m. on a weekday, so it wasn't busy. I liked having a low-key dinner at the end of all that
        walking.</p>
    <br/>
    <picalt>insxml:ide cafe la boheme shinjuku gyoen</picalt>
    <p>The big windows, servers' uniforms and upstairs kitchen all reminded me of Your Name. I
        ordered the pizza with tomato and ground meat. It was delicious <comment>and dxml:idn't have any
            toothpicks in it either</comment>.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>The other food and drinks were also quite tasty, and the price was reasonable for a nice
        restaurant like this. I would come back here even when I'm not on an <term ref="anime"
            >anime</term> pilgrimage.</p>
    <br/>

    <p>FOLLOWING THE RED THREAD TO YOUR NAME LOCATIONS</p>
    <p>THERE'S ALSO A FICTIONAL CITY IN THE MOVIE CALLED, ITOMORICHŌ. IF YOU LIKE THIS ARTICLE,
        MAYBE I'LL GO TO HIDA AND LAKE SUWA <comment>THE PLACES THAT INSPIRED IT</comment> FOR A
        SECOND YOUR NAME PILGRIMAGE.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>Unfortunately, I couldn't cover all the sacred Your Name spots in Tokyo, but I think this
        itinerary is a successful one day walking tour with enough time to enjoy each location.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>Taking photos of things I'd seen dozens of times in the movie, but never actually experienced
        was so much fun. It was like a scavenger hunt! Finding little connections between the actual
        location and Your Name <comment>like the beer garden sign</comment> was very rewarding. I
        told you about a few of these little details, but I'm sure you'll find even more when you go
        yourself.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>And you should go soon. <person xml:id="jjabrams">JJ Abrams</person> just started work on a
        live action Hollywood adaptation of Your Name <comment>which I'm sure will be stellar
            😒</comment>. With popularity growing, these spots are bound to get more and more
        crowded as time goes on.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>Of course, the real life Your Name locations are not as beautiful as they are in the film.
        After all, there aren't any gigantic animators airbrushing the streets of Tokyo each day.
        But seeing the inspirations for Shinkai Makoto's imaginative story was a wonderful
        experience. It gave me a much deeper connection to the film and city.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>As I'm sure you already know <comment>because you're a huge Your Name fan like me</comment>,
        there's another city in the movie called, <loc xml:id="itomoricho">Itomorichō</loc>. It's
        the rural town where <char ref="mitsuha">Mitsuha</char> grew up. Unfortunately, <loc
            ref="itomoricho">Itomorichō</loc> is not real; it's a completely fictional place, but
        some Your Name pilgrims have been visiting Hxml:ida in Gifu and Lake Suwa in Nagano, which were
        both models for <loc ref="itomoricho">Itomorichō</loc>.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>If you like this article, maybe I'll go there for a second Your Name pilgrimage. That way we
        can get out of <loc ref="tokyo">Tokyo</loc> and experience Japanese life in the inaka. If
        you're itching for a sequel pilgrimage, let us know on Facebook, Twitter, or old-fashioned
        email.</p>
    <br/>
    <p>See you at <loc ref="suga">Suga Shrine</loc>!</p>
</xml>
