<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
    <para type="pretext"><person type="sender">Coffin</person>, a member of the American
        Anti-Slavery Society, writes to author and abolitionist Lydia Maria Child about Harriet
        Jacobs. <quote>"I hope you will call &amp; see, if she is now in the city, one of the most
            interesting cases of escape from slavery that you have ever seen."</quote>
    </para>
    <letter>
        <person type="receipent">Phila. <date>25 June 1842</date></person>
        <greeting>Esteemed Friend,</greeting>
        <content>
            <sent>... I hope you will call &amp; see, if she is now in the city, one of the most
                interesting cases of escape from slavery that you have ever seen.</sent>
            <sent>She was sent from this city yesterday morning &amp;' consigned to Mr.
                Johnston.</sent>
            <sent>She is from N.C. was brought away by a sea captain. She was sold by her master to
                the speculators &amp; to avoid being sent away she was hidden for 7 years! in a
                small upper room of a house occupied by colored people &amp; within a hundred yards
                of her master's house, who did not know she was there.</sent>
            <sent>She had not seen her boy, for 7 years till within 3 days of her coming
                away.</sent>
            <sent>She has been shut up so long that she can hardly walk. Another woman was brought
                away from Delaware, who was found tied to a tree.</sent>
            <sent>If Mr. Johnston was the man he ought to be, he would invite you occasionally to
                see some of these remarkable cases, which are continually passing from Phil. to
                N.Y.</sent>
            <sent><word type="strikeout">The Vagrant</word> what a queer mistake. The Vigilance
                Committee of this city are doing a fine business in weakening &amp; delapidating the
                edifice of slavery.</sent>
            <sent>Success to them...</sent>
        </content>
        <person type="sender">Joshua Coffin</person>
    </letter>
    <para>
        <heading>Citation:</heading>
        <cite>Autograph letter, signed; Anti-Slavery Collection, Boston Public Library; Lydia Maria
            Child Papers, The Collected Correspondence of Lydia Maria Child, 1817-1880, ed. Patricia
            G. Holland and Milton Meltzer. Millwood, N.Y.: Kraus Microfilm, 1980. 14:389—4</cite>
    </para>
</text>
