<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--2020-09-30 ebb: DIGIT 110 EXAM FILE. 
    The only change you should make to this file is to add the schema association to validate it.
    Do not change the XML elements or attributes here, but make changes to the schema file so that it 
    validates this XML document.
    You'll be submitting your corrected schema file and this XML file on Canvas. -->

<xml>
    <headline>Penn State Behrend opens new Wintergreen Gorge trail system</headline>
    <date when="2020-09-22">September 22, 2020</date>
    <location>ERIE, Pa.</location>
    <source url="https://behrend.psu.edu/story/53651/2020/09/22/penn-state-behrend-opens-new-wintergreen-gorge-trail-system"/>
    <listPerson>
        <person id="RFord">
            <name>Ralph Ford</name>
            <role>
                <roleName>Chancellor</roleName>
                <organization>Penn State Erie, The Behrend College</organization>
            </role>
        </person>
        <person id="SMason">
            <name>Sherri "Sam" Mason</name>
            <role>
                <roleName>Sustainability Coordinator</roleName>
                <organization>Penn State Erie, The Behrend College</organization>
            </role>
        </person>
    </listPerson>
    <body>
        <p n="1">With a ribbon-cutting and a short walk on the new bamboo boardwalk, <organization>Penn State Behrend</organization>
            formally opened the renovated trail system in <place>Wintergreen Gorge</place>, a Natural Heritage Area
            on and adjacent to the <place>Behrend campus</place>.</p>

        <p n="2">The college recently completed a <fund currency="USD">$690,000</fund> trail improvement project, which will reduce
            erosion in the gorge while maintaining public access to the property, which is now
            ADA-accessible for the first time.</p>

        <p n="3"><quote ref="RFord">The gorge is a public resource,</quote> Penn State Behrend Chancellor
            Ralph Ford said. <quote ref="RFord">We want to protect it for the generations that will
                use it in the future.</quote></p>

        <p n="4">Funding for the trail project, which began in 2013, was provided by the <organization>Pennsylvania
            Department of Conservation and Natural Resources</organization>, <organization>the Pennsylvania Department of
            Community and Economic Development</organization>, <organization>the Erie County Planning Department</organization> and <organization>Penn
            State</organization>.</p>

        <p n="5">The improvements include a 165-foot boardwalk, which extends the primary trail over a wet
            area. The structure will encourage visitors to remain on the trail, which is the spine
            of a 14-mile network of informal “shortcut” paths, many of which have accelerated
            erosion in the gorge.</p>

        <p n="6">The primary trail has been topped with a compacted aggregate, making it accessible to
            visitors with strollers, or even wheelchairs.</p>
        
        <p n="7"> <quote ref="SMason">Being part of a community means you think about others as well as yourself,</quote> said
            Sherri “Sam” Mason, the sustainability coordinator at Penn State Behrend. <quote ref="SMason">Our students
            have good access to the gorge, but we want everyone else to enjoy it, too. That includes
            people with mobility issues.</quote></p>

        <p n="8"><quote ref="SMason">There are so few green spaces that offer this level of accessibility,</quote> she said.</p>

        <p n="9">The project also created a new trailhead at <place>Cooper Road</place>, where a parking area now offers
            space for 17 vehicles. Additional parking is available at the <place>Ohio Hall</place> and <place>School of
            Science</place> trailheads on <place>the Behrend campus</place>.</p>

        <p n="10">The college has secured <fund currency="USD">$380,000</fund> in funding for the next phase of the trail project, which
            will extend the aggregate-topped path to <place>Trout Run</place>. That work is expected to begin in
            the fall of <date when="2021">2021</date>.</p>
        <p n="11"> <quote ref="SMason">We need some time to see how this first phase improves things, particularly in regard
            to the water coming off the <place>Bayfront Connector</place>,</quote> Mason said. <quote ref="SMason">We’ll make adjustments,
            and we’ll develop a plan that further improves public access to the gorge while
            protecting the natural environment for the generations that follow us.</quote></p>
    </body>
</xml>
